- So how was work today?
- Busy.
(Girl:)I removed an appendix, a gall bladder
and about a foot and a half of bowel.
I'm hoping that was three different guys.
[CHUCKLES]
(Girl:)No, just the one.
(Girl:)He didn't make it.
(Girl:)So how was your day?
(Leonard:)You know, I'm a physicist,
so I thought about stuff.
- That's it?
- I wrote some of it down.
[LAUGHS]
- Are you done eating?
- Yeah.
(Girl:)Oh, good.
(Leonard:)If I knew you were waiting,
I would have swallowed that lasagna whole.
[PHONE RINGS]
STEPHANIE [ON RECORDING]:
You've reached Dr. Stephanie Barnett.
(Phone rings. Answering machine:)Leave a message.
[PHONE BEEPS]
HOWARD:
Hey, Steph, it's me again, Howard.
(Howard(voice):)If you're free Friday, maybe we could
have something to eat at my place.
(Howard(voice):)My mom cooks a hell of a brisket.